1
00:00:15,750 --> 00:00:17,270
Ok, ok here we go.

2
00:00:19,290 --> 00:00:20,610
So lonely!

3
00:00:22,430 --> 00:00:23,580
Stiff!

4
00:00:24,559 --> 00:00:25,359
Ha!

5
00:00:25,360 --> 00:00:26,410
I can't do that!

6
00:00:27,600 --> 00:00:28,250
Come on Elsa.

7
00:00:28,260 --> 00:00:29,780
This is for Anna.
You can do this.

8
00:00:29,900 --> 00:00:30,580
Relax!

9
00:00:30,730 --> 00:00:31,950
It looks great.

10
00:00:32,640 --> 00:00:34,500
I just want it to be perfect.

11
00:00:34,600 --> 00:00:35,690
Speaking of perfect.

12
00:00:35,690 --> 00:00:37,920
CHEAK this out!

13
00:00:40,830 --> 00:00:43,760
Kristoff, are you sure i can leave
you In charge here?

14
00:00:43,760 --> 00:00:44,600
Absolutely.

15
00:00:44,810 --> 00:00:47,500
Because i dont want anything that happens
of this core yard.

16
00:00:47,500 --> 00:00:49,600
What could happen?
It's all set.

17
00:00:49,600 --> 00:00:51,600
Olaf! What are you doing?

18
00:00:52,660 --> 00:00:54,110
I'm not eating cake!

19
00:00:54,160 --> 00:00:55,410
Olaf...

20
00:00:55,590 --> 00:00:57,700
But it's an ICE CREAM cake!

21
00:00:57,700 --> 00:00:59,150
And it's for Anna.

22
00:00:59,150 --> 00:01:01,550
And it's for Anna!

23
00:01:04,000 --> 00:01:04,790
Oh, it's time!

24
00:01:04,790 --> 00:01:05,800
It's time...

25
00:01:06,240 --> 00:01:07,050
For what?

26
00:01:07,119 --> 00:01:08,119
Ok...ehh!

27
00:01:08,120 --> 00:01:09,460
you sure you got this?

28
00:01:09,460 --> 00:01:10,360
I'm sure.

29
00:01:10,510 --> 00:01:12,020
Dont let anyone in before
we are ready.

30
00:01:12,030 --> 00:01:13,730
- I won't.
- And don't touch anything.

31
00:01:13,730 --> 00:01:15,530
I'm just gonna stand here.

32
00:01:15,530 --> 00:01:17,230
I'm probably gonna walk around
a little.

33
00:01:17,230 --> 00:01:19,230
Keep in eye on that cake!

34
00:01:20,620 --> 00:01:22,620
She thinks you are an idiot.

35
00:01:22,920 --> 00:01:24,920
Well, clearly she is wrong.

36
00:01:27,290 --> 00:01:28,440
What? its fine.

37
00:01:28,440 --> 00:01:30,380
I cant breath...

38
00:01:30,390 --> 00:01:31,710
...or smell.

39
00:01:34,500 --> 00:01:35,100
Psst!!

40
00:01:35,100 --> 00:01:36,120
Anna!

41
00:01:36,120 --> 00:01:37,120
Ya?

42
00:01:37,330 --> 00:01:39,220
Happy birthday...

43
00:01:39,850 --> 00:01:41,220
...to you.

44
00:01:41,370 --> 00:01:42,820
It's your birthday!

45
00:01:43,770 --> 00:01:45,770
To me...

46
00:01:45,940 --> 00:01:47,170
it's my birthday...

47
00:01:47,340 --> 00:01:48,490
Come on!

48
00:01:49,150 --> 00:01:50,450
It's my birthday?

49
00:01:50,950 --> 00:01:53,370
it's going to be perfect because...

50
00:01:53,370 --> 00:01:57,000
You've never had a real
birthday before.

51
00:01:57,000 --> 00:02:01,070
Except of course the one just
spends out side my locked door.

52
00:02:01,320 --> 00:02:04,700
So i'm here way too late
to help you celebrate.

53
00:02:04,700 --> 00:02:08,510
And be your birthday Tate
if i may...

54
00:02:08,510 --> 00:02:09,550
Achoo...

55
00:02:13,340 --> 00:02:16,920
Elsa, am thinking you might
have a cold.

56
00:02:16,920 --> 00:02:19,290
I don't get colds, besides...

57
00:02:19,290 --> 00:02:22,660
Cold never bothered me Anyway.

58
00:02:22,660 --> 00:02:23,560
Wow!!

59
00:02:27,880 --> 00:02:29,150
Fancy.

60
00:02:29,230 --> 00:02:30,440
Just follow the String.

61
00:02:30,440 --> 00:02:32,170
Wait, what?

62
00:02:32,590 --> 00:02:36,410
I got big plans i can surprises
for today.

63
00:02:36,660 --> 00:02:40,400
Nothing but nothings can
get in our way.

64
00:02:40,390 --> 00:02:44,550
I've worked For weeks plans
everything within my power.

65
00:02:44,830 --> 00:02:48,780
I even got Kristoff and Sven
to take shower.

66
00:02:48,800 --> 00:02:52,500
If someone wants to hold me back.

67
00:02:52,500 --> 00:02:56,160
I'd like to see their try.

68
00:02:56,170 --> 00:02:56,850
Summer!

69
00:02:56,900 --> 00:03:00,830
I come for birthday plan attack.

70
00:03:00,830 --> 00:03:03,840
I'm giving you the sun, moon and sky.

71
00:03:07,760 --> 00:03:09,760
little brother!

72
00:03:10,490 --> 00:03:13,500
I'm making today a perfect day for you.

73
00:03:13,500 --> 00:03:14,430
Oh, sandwich.

74
00:03:14,440 --> 00:03:18,250
I'm making today a blast if it's the
last thing i do.

75
00:03:18,250 --> 00:03:22,560
but everything you are to me
and all you've been through.

76
00:03:22,560 --> 00:03:27,980
i'm making today a perfect day for you.

77
00:03:28,909 --> 00:03:29,909
Achoo...

78
00:03:30,910 --> 00:03:32,300
- Achoo...
- they coming thrice.

79
00:03:32,370 --> 00:03:33,570
I'm fine.

80
00:03:39,660 --> 00:03:42,470
surprise, surprise this one is specially...

81
00:03:42,470 --> 00:03:42,870
Achoo...

82
00:03:42,870 --> 00:03:47,810
Wow! you've got me really
but i still concerned for you.

83
00:03:47,810 --> 00:03:52,050
I think it's time that you go home
and get some rest.

84
00:03:52,280 --> 00:03:55,720
We are not stopping cause
next one is the best.

85
00:03:59,213 --> 00:04:02,900
Elsa, you gotta go lie down.

86
00:04:02,900 --> 00:04:07,030
No way we have to paint the town.

87
00:04:07,030 --> 00:04:10,300
but you need medical attention.

88
00:04:10,210 --> 00:04:15,510
Are you sick?
How about cold remedy of my own invention.

89
00:04:15,610 --> 00:04:17,480
- No thanks.
- we'll take it.

90
00:04:17,480 --> 00:04:20,050
We're making today a perfect day
for you...

91
00:04:20,050 --> 00:04:21,350
...Making Today a special day.

92
00:04:21,350 --> 00:04:25,150
We singing a birthday song to make
your wishes come true.

93
00:04:25,250 --> 00:04:27,850
- your wished come true.
- we love princess Anna.

94
00:04:28,542 --> 00:04:30,860
And i love you too.

95
00:04:30,860 --> 00:04:33,090
We're making today a perfect day...

96
00:04:33,160 --> 00:04:37,090
happy birthday in every way
i'm making today a perfect day.

97
00:04:37,218 --> 00:04:38,730
I can fix it!

98
00:04:39,387 --> 00:04:40,630
No, no! ah!

99
00:04:44,670 --> 00:04:46,040
All fixed!

100
00:04:46,861 --> 00:04:48,861
Dry banana hippy hat?

101
00:04:48,860 --> 00:04:51,200
Come on.
Now we climb.

102
00:04:51,200 --> 00:04:53,550
Elsa, thats too much.
you need to rest.

103
00:04:53,550 --> 00:04:57,680
we need to get to our birthday cheers,
I mean wells.

104
00:04:57,680 --> 00:05:00,980
Make a dreams, make a plans...

105
00:05:00,980 --> 00:05:03,450
Go go! Go go!

106
00:05:04,345 --> 00:05:07,660
Follow the sheer to the end,
You are my very best friend.

107
00:05:07,660 --> 00:05:10,030
- Elsa?
- What? I'm fine.

108
00:05:10,030 --> 00:05:12,700
We gonna fly, we gonna sing.

109
00:05:13,554 --> 00:05:16,200
Follow the string to the thing.

110
00:05:16,357 --> 00:05:18,400
Happy! Happy! Happy!

111
00:05:18,400 --> 00:05:19,240
Merry! Merry! Merry!

112
00:05:19,240 --> 00:05:23,000
Hot... cold... hot... big day

113
00:05:23,000 --> 00:05:25,240
Elsa, look at you. you've got a fever.

114
00:05:25,240 --> 00:05:26,550
you've burning up.

115
00:05:26,550 --> 00:05:30,580
Alright, we can't go on like this.

116
00:05:30,580 --> 00:05:34,150
Let's put this day on hold.

117
00:05:34,375 --> 00:05:38,520
Come on, admit it to yourself.

118
00:05:39,150 --> 00:05:43,560
Ok, i have a cold.

119
00:05:45,419 --> 00:05:46,800
I'm sorry Anna.

120
00:05:46,800 --> 00:05:49,600
i just wanna to give you one
perfect birthday.

121
00:05:49,690 --> 00:05:52,500
But i ruined it. Again.

122
00:05:52,500 --> 00:05:54,400
You didn ruined anything.

123
00:05:54,400 --> 00:05:56,140
let you just get to the bed.

124
00:05:56,764 --> 00:05:58,910
Oh! no, please stop!

125
00:05:58,910 --> 00:06:00,650
surprise!

126
00:06:00,650 --> 00:06:02,480
Wow!!

127
00:06:02,480 --> 00:06:03,720
Wow!

128
00:06:03,738 --> 00:06:07,420
Making today a perfect day for you.

129
00:06:07,949 --> 00:06:11,460
We making today smiley and shiny
and new.

130
00:06:11,879 --> 00:06:14,160
there is a fine line between chaos.

131
00:06:14,160 --> 00:06:15,860
And hullabaloo.

132
00:06:16,317 --> 00:06:19,830
Making today a perfect day.
Making today a perfect day.

133
00:06:19,830 --> 00:06:22,500
A... N... N... A...!!

134
00:06:22,500 --> 00:06:24,500
Making today a perfect day for you.

135
00:06:24,500 --> 00:06:26,370
Happy birthday.

136
00:06:26,370 --> 00:06:30,450
- Making today a happy day and no feel ever blue.
- I love you baby!

137
00:06:30,450 --> 00:06:33,410
For everything you ever was
and all that you do.

138
00:06:33,410 --> 00:06:34,710
I do.

139
00:06:34,710 --> 00:06:38,280
Making today a perfect day for you.
Making today a perfect day for you.

140
00:06:40,775 --> 00:06:42,100
Perfect day!

141
00:06:42,100 --> 00:06:43,420
OK. To bed with you.

142
00:06:43,420 --> 00:06:47,380
Wait, wait all thats left to do is with the queen
and blow the birthday horn.

143
00:06:47,330 --> 00:06:48,260
- No, no, no...
- achoo...

144
00:06:58,793 --> 00:07:01,000
Best birthday present ever.

145
00:07:01,000 --> 00:07:02,000
Which one?

146
00:07:02,530 --> 00:07:04,610
You letting me take care of you.

147
00:07:04,610 --> 00:07:05,240
Achoo...

148
00:07:14,475 --> 00:07:16,920
This way, Sluje and Slud and Slive
and Ansel...

149
00:07:16,930 --> 00:07:19,500
And Veiken, Fredge, Flurry, Palory
and Crystal...

150
00:07:19,800 --> 00:07:23,000
- And Squalen and Tag, Speared...
- The end william.

151
00:07:23,784 --> 00:07:24,900
Don't ask!

